news and that is ICC Lombard let's pull
it up last time I checked it was up
about 4% thereabouts now the news here
is that there is a block deal and it
seems it could be a possibility that the
parent bank is actually increasing its
stake via some of these blocks Yash has
the details Yash morning tell us more
well SOI good morning so of course as
far as this particular transaction which
happened today morning is concerned it
was in the pipeline for about 6 months
ICICI Bank in September
2023 received the insurance Regulators
approval to up its stake in the general
insurance subsidiary that is IC Lombard
by about 4% uh a part of that
transaction has been executed today so
about 1.4% stake has changed hands as
far as IC Lombard is concerned sources
tell us that the parent Bank as you
alluded to IC bank is the buyer as far
as this particular block deal is
concerned as far as the seller is
concerned uh that according to our
sources is bti Enterprises now after
this particular transaction bti
Enterprises take in ic Lombard is like
likely to reduce to about 2.3% from the
current 3.7% whereas ICICI Bank stake in
ICI Lombard is expected to increase to
49.3 1% from the current
47.91 per. uh two important things to
look forward to as far as this
particular stock IC Lombard is concerned
IC bank has of course the intention to
raise its stake to Beyond 50% which
means it will look to acquire uh that
additional 2 and a half% stake in C
Lombard and bti Enterprise which is
essentially left with about just about
2.3% stake will look to dilute that
stake as well going
forward all right yes big developments
there on ICI Lombard the parent company
looking the IC Bank looking to increase
its take there let's take a short break